<?xml version='1.0'?><rss version='2.0'><channel><title>India One-Liners</title><item><title>- Rajasthan Patwari Exam 2025: RSSB Issues New Guidelines For Patwari Exam, Details Here — In one sentence: Rajasthan Patwari Exam 2025: RSSB Issues New Guidelines For Patwari Exam, Details Here (via ndtv.com)</title><link>https://www.ndtv.com/education/rajasthan-patwari-exam-2025-rssb-issues-new-guidelines-for-patwari-exam-details-here-9096348#publisher=newsstand</link></item><item><title>- The Big Restaurant That Failed Veganism — In one sentence: A look at some of the key stories in the world of finance this week. (via livemint.com)</title><link>https://www.livemint.com/companies/news/the-big-restaurant-that-failed-veganism-11755325225383.html</link></item><item><title>- iOS 26 brings a new AI-powered feature to extend your iPhone's battery life: Here's how it works — In one sentence: iOS 26 brings a new AI-powered feature to extend your iPhone's battery life: Here's how it works (via livemint.com)</title><link>https://www.livemint.com/technology/tech-news/ios-26-brings-a-new-ai-powered-feature-to-extend-your-iphones-battery-life-heres-how-it-works-11755323139875.html</link></item><item><title>- 1.4 Lakh Users Buy New FASTag Annual Pass On Day One — In one sentence: 1.4 Lakh Users Buy New FASTag Annual Pass On Day One (via ndtv.com)</title><link>https://www.ndtv.com/india-news/1-4-lakh-users-buy-national-highways-authority-of-indias-new-fastag-annual-pass-on-day-one-9096416#publisher=newsstand</link></item><item><title>- Regaal Resources IPO allotment status: Allotment date in focus. GMP, how to check IPO allotment status online — In one sentence: Regaal Resources IPO allotment status: Allotment date in focus. (via livemint.com)</title><link>https://www.livemint.com/market/ipo/regaal-resources-ipo-allotment-status-allotment-date-in-focus-gmp-how-to-check-ipo-allotment-status-online-11755323090250.html</link></item><item><title>- Ministry Of Education Offers Five Free AI Courses On Swayam Portal, Details Here — In one sentence: Ministry Of Education Offers Five Free AI Courses On Swayam Portal, Details Here (via ndtv.com)</title><link>https://www.ndtv.com/education/ministry-of-education-offers-five-free-artificial-intelligence-courses-on-swayam-portal-9096123#publisher=newsstand</link></item><item><title>- Vivo T4 Pro confirmed to launch in India soon: Expected price, specifications and all you need to know — In one sentence: Vivo T4 Pro confirmed to launch in India soon: Expected price, specifications and all you need to know (via livemint.com)</title><link>https://www.livemint.com/technology/gadgets/vivo-t4-pro-confirmed-to-launch-in-india-soon-expected-price-specifications-and-all-you-need-to-know-11755318437339.html</link></item><item><title>- S&amp;P Upgrade to Boost Foreign Flows, Lower Funding Costs for Indian Companies: Vishal Goenka — In one sentence: Watch the video to find out more about S&P upgrade to boost foreign flows, lower funding costs for Indian companies. (via economictimes.indiatimes.com)</title><link>https://economictimes.indiatimes.com/markets/expert-view/sp-upgrade-to-boost-foreign-flows-lower-funding-costs-for-indian-companies-vishal-goenka/articleshow/123329770.cms</link></item><item><title>- Lawrence Bishnoi gang members held for ‘Independence Day terror plot’, police say — In one sentence: Police in the western Indian city of Mumbai say they have foiled a terror plot ahead of the 70th Independence Day. (via indianexpress.com)</title><link>https://indianexpress.com/article/india/lawrence-bishnoi-gang-members-held-for-independence-day-terror-plot-police-10192554/</link></item><item><title>- Air Canada cancels all flights as flight attendants go on strike — In one sentence: Air Canada cancels all flights as flight attendants go on strike (via livemint.com)</title><link>https://www.livemint.com/companies/news/air-canada-cancels-all-flights-as-flight-attendants-go-on-strike-11755322752741.html</link></item><item><title>- Holy trinity of promoters, FIIs and DIIs bought these 21 stocks. Can they be the next big stars? — In one sentence: India's foreign institutional investors (FIIs) and domestic institutional investors (DIIs) have bought a record amount of shares in the first two months of the current financial year. (via economictimes.indiatimes.com)</title><link>https://economictimes.indiatimes.com/markets/stocks/news/holy-trinity-of-promoters-fiis-and-diis-bought-these-21-stocks-can-they-be-the-next-big-stars/articleshow/123329730.cms</link></item><item><title>- Man Throws Rice During Court Proceedings In Delhi, Black Magic Suspected — In one sentence: Man Throws Rice During Court Proceedings In Delhi, Black Magic Suspected (via ndtv.com)</title><link>https://www.ndtv.com/india-news/delhi-court-jails-man-for-throwing-rice-during-judicial-proceeding-9096256#publisher=newsstand</link></item><item><title>- First Isro-Nasa collaboration satellite NISAR’s antenna reflector deployed in space — In one sentence: The Indian Space Research Organisation (Isro) and the National Space Agency of India (Nasa) have successfully deployed a reflector on the NISAR satellite. (via indianexpress.com)</title><link>https://indianexpress.com/article/india/first-isro-nasa-collaboration-satellite-nisar-antenna-reflector-deployed-space-10192529/</link></item><item><title>- IIT Bombay’s Eureka! 2025 Returns, Offering Startups Mentorship, Funding & INR 2 Cr In Prizes — In one sentence: Here is a round-up of some of the most interesting technology-related stories from India this week. (via inc42.com)</title><link>https://inc42.com/buzz/iit-bombays-eureka-2025-returns-offering-startups-mentorship-funding-inr-2-cr-in-prizes/</link></item><item><title>- Power Grid, Suzlon, UltraTech among 5 stocks with 28% potential upside. Here's why — In one sentence: Watch The Economic Times' special report on 5 stocks with potential upside. (via economictimes.indiatimes.com)</title><link>https://economictimes.indiatimes.com/markets/stocks/news/power-grid-suzlon-ultratech-among-5-stocks-with-28-potential-upside-heres-why/slideshow/123329532.cms</link></item><item><title>- Swiggy Raises Platform Fee To Rs 14, Marks 600% Hike In Two Years — In one sentence: Swiggy Raises Platform Fee To Rs 14, Marks 600% Hike In Two Years (via ndtv.com)</title><link>https://www.ndtv.com/india-news/swiggy-raises-platform-fee-by-rs-2-marks-600-hike-in-two-years-9096170#publisher=newsstand</link></item><item><title>- Anand James sees Muthoot Finance shares rallying to Rs 3,000 after breakout on Q1 beat — In one sentence: Watch the video to know more about Anand James Muthoot Finance. (via economictimes.indiatimes.com)</title><link>https://economictimes.indiatimes.com/markets/expert-view/anand-james-sees-muthoot-finance-shares-rallying-to-rs-3000-after-breakout-on-q1-beat/articleshow/123329437.cms</link></item><item><title>- Investors react to US-Russia summit reaching no agreement — In one sentence: Investors react to US-Russia summit reaching no agreement - The Economic Times Benchmark, 24,631 (via economictimes.indiatimes.com)</title><link>https://economictimes.indiatimes.com/markets/stocks/news/investors-react-to-us-russia-summit-reaching-no-agreement/articleshow/123329403.cms</link></item><item><title>- Stocks to buy under  ₹200: Mehul Kothari of Anand Rathi recommends three shares to buy or sell — In one sentence: Stocks to buy under 200: Mehul Kothari of Anand Rathi recommends three shares to buy or sell (via livemint.com)</title><link>https://www.livemint.com/market/stock-market-news/stocks-to-buy-under-rs-200-mehul-kothari-of-anand-rathi-recommends-three-shares-to-buy-or-sell-11755318887555.html</link></item><item><title>- Ola Electric rolls out sports scooter line, announces two cell variants and AI-powered platform — In one sentence: Ola Electric rolls out sports scooter line, announces two cell variants and AI-powered platform (via yourstory.com)</title><link>https://yourstory.com/2025/08/ola-electric-sports-scooter-line-cell-variants-ai-powered-platform</link></item><item><title>- Do you need a TV anymore? I used the Lumio Arc 7 to get a better picture — In one sentence: Lumio Arc 7 projector review skip to content (via indianexpress.com)</title><link>https://indianexpress.com/article/technology/tech-reviews/lumio-arc-7-review-10192421/</link></item><item><title>- PM Modi pays tributes to Vajpayee on death anniversary — In one sentence: Prime Minister Narendra Modi has paid tribute to former Prime Minister Atal Bihari Vajpayee on his death anniversary. (via indianexpress.com)</title><link>https://indianexpress.com/article/india/pm-modi-tributes-atal-bihari-vajpayee-death-anniversary-10192424/</link></item><item><title>- Meta plans fourth restructuring of AI efforts in six months — In one sentence: Meta, a leading artificial intelligence (AI) start-up, has announced a restructuring of its operations in India. (via indianexpress.com)</title><link>https://indianexpress.com/article/technology/meta-plans-fourth-restructuring-of-ai-efforts-in-six-months-10192412/</link></item><item><title>- GST reforms: What may get cheaper after Narendra Modi's next-generation Goods and Services Tax in India? — In one sentence: India's new Goods and Services Tax (GST) regime came into effect on 1 July, but what does it mean for consumers? (via livemint.com)</title><link>https://www.livemint.com/market/stock-market-news/gst-reforms-what-may-get-cheaper-after-narendra-modis-next-generation-goods-and-services-tax-in-india-11755315915136.html</link></item><item><title>- Bank Holiday Today: Are banks open or closed today on Saturday, August 16? Check here — In one sentence: Are banks open or closed today on Saturday, August 16? (via indianexpress.com)</title><link>https://indianexpress.com/article/india/bank-holiday-today-are-banks-open-or-closed-today-on-saturday-august-16-check-here-10192349/</link></item><item><title>- The gilded gambler: Dwarkanath Tagore's rise and ruin in colonial Bengal — In one sentence: A look back at some of the key events that shaped Indian history. (via livemint.com)</title><link>https://www.livemint.com/companies/people/dwarkanath-tagore-bengal-british-empire-history-capitalism-business-collapse-11755157589217.html</link></item><item><title>- HAL vs Bharat Dynamics vs Mazagon Dock Shipbuilders: Which defence PSU stock to buy after Q1 results 2025? — In one sentence: What are India's biggest defence companies? (via livemint.com)</title><link>https://www.livemint.com/market/stock-market-news/hal-vs-bharat-dynamics-vs-mazagon-dock-shipbuilders-which-defence-psu-stock-to-buy-after-q1-results-2025-11755313254775.html</link></item><item><title>- Treasuries Mixed; Short End Closing a Volatile Week With Gains — In one sentence: A look at the key economic and market stories of the week. (via livemint.com)</title><link>https://www.livemint.com/market/stock-market-news/treasuries-mixed-short-end-closing-a-volatile-week-with-gains-11755313368930.html</link></item><item><title>- Handpicked Monitor Deals for you: Up to 75% off on the best monitors from top brands — In one sentence: India is the world's biggest producer and exporter of gold and silver, according to the World Gold Council. (via livemint.com)</title><link>https://www.livemint.com/technology/gadgets/handpicked-monitor-deals-for-you-up-to-75-off-on-the-best-monitors-from-top-brands-11755175694422.html</link></item><item><title>- ChatGPT may be a little different now as OpenAI rolls out a new ‘warmer and friendlier’ update — In one sentence: It’s the world’s largest artificial intelligence-powered trading platform. (via livemint.com)</title><link>https://www.livemint.com/technology/tech-news/chatgpt-may-be-a-little-different-now-as-openai-rolls-out-a-warmer-and-friendlier-update-gpt-5-sam-altman-nick-turley-11755309247502.html</link></item><item><title>- China’s Top Rival to Tesla Bot Headlines Robot Games in Beijing — In one sentence: A daily guide to the key stories, newspaper headlines and quotes from the news. (via livemint.com)</title><link>https://www.livemint.com/technology/tech-news/chinas-top-rival-to-tesla-bot-headlines-robot-games-in-beijing-11755307264816.html</link></item><item><title>- ‘Tech for good ideas’ are fine, but it is impact at scale that matters: Anjali Bansal, founder, Avaana Capital — In one sentence: In our series of letters from Indian journalists, film-maker and columnist Sharmila Tagore reflects on the changing face of technology in India. (via indianexpress.com)</title><link>https://indianexpress.com/article/technology/tech-news-technology/tech-for-good-impact-at-scale-anjali-bansal-avaana-capital-founder-10191330/</link></item><item><title>- A Trump Intel stake could make national security the new ‘too big to fail’ — In one sentence: US President Donald Trump is in talks to buy a stake in chipmaker Intel, according to people close to the matter. (via livemint.com)</title><link>https://www.livemint.com/companies/a-trump-intel-stake-could-make-national-security-the-new-too-big-to-fail-11755272995840.html</link></item><item><title>- Omar owes an apology, not a signature campaign: Opposition tears into CM over statehood ‘theatrics’ — In one sentence: Omar Abdullah owes an apology, not a signature campaign: Opposition tears into CM over statehood ‘theatrics’ (via indianexpress.com)</title><link>https://indianexpress.com/article/india/omar-owes-an-apology-not-a-signature-campaign-oppn-tears-into-cm-over-statehood-theatrics-10191994/</link></item><item><title>- Marijuana shops sue New York after they were allowed to open too close to schools — In one sentence: A look back at some of the top business stories over the past seven days. (via livemint.com)</title><link>https://www.livemint.com/companies/news/marijuana-shops-sue-new-york-after-they-were-allowed-to-open-too-close-to-schools-11755296149746.html</link></item><item><title>- Ola Electric Unveils New Scooter, Cuts Prices Of S1 Pro Plus, Roadster X Plus — In one sentence: Here is a round-up of some of the most interesting technology-related stories from India this week. (via inc42.com)</title><link>https://inc42.com/buzz/ola-electric-unveils-new-scooter-cuts-prices-of-s1-pro-plus-roadster-x-plus/</link></item><item><title>- Zoomcar’s Loss Zooms 66% YoY To $4.2 Mn In June Quarter — In one sentence: Zoomcar's loss of 66% to $4.2 Mn in June quarter Skip to content Zoomcar's loss of 66% to $4.2 Mn in June quarter (via inc42.com)</title><link>https://inc42.com/buzz/zoomcars-loss-zooms-66-yoy-to-4-2-mn-in-june-quarter/</link></item><item><title>- From blockchain to bitcoin: Charting India’s next leap in jobs, AI, and energy — In one sentence: From blockchain to bitcoin: Charting India’s next leap in jobs, AI, and energy (via yourstory.com)</title><link>https://yourstory.com/2025/08/blockchain-bitcoin-charting-india-next-leap-jobs-ai-energy-linkedin</link></item><item><title>- Swiggy hikes platform fee amid festive surge: Report — In one sentence: Swiggy hikes platform fee amid festive surge: Report (via yourstory.com)</title><link>https://yourstory.com/2025/08/swiggy-hikes-platform-fee-amid-festive-surge</link></item><item><title>- Indian Soonicorn Tracker: List Of India’s Unicorns Of Tomorrow — In one sentence: In our series of letters from Indian journalists, Soonicorn looks at some of the most read stories of the week. (via inc42.com)</title><link>https://inc42.com/features/indian-soonicorn-tracker-list-of-indias-unicorns-of-tomorrow/</link></item></channel></rss>